Search

Sign UpSign up for our Newsletter

Search

Toggle navigation

* [Hunger  
    in America](https://www.feedingamerica.org/hunger-in-america)
* [Our  
    Work](https://www.feedingamerica.org/our-work)
* [Take  
    Action](https://www.feedingamerica.org/take-action)
* [Find a  
    Food bank](https://www.feedingamerica.org/find-your-local-foodbank)
* [Hunger  
    Blog](https://www.feedingamerica.org/hunger-blog)

1. [Privacy Policy](https://www.feedingamerica.org/privacy-policy)
2. Donor Privacy Policy

Donor Privacy Policy
====================

_Updated November 30, 2015_

As a donor submitting personally identifying information (“Personal Information”) to us or any of our staff, you consent to the terms and conditions of the policy and to our processing and use of Personal Information for the purposes stated below. 

**Personal Information**

“Personal Information” is information that identifies you personally, such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address. We collect and store the personally identifiable information that you have provided us via one of the email addresses identified on our website or when you otherwise contact us in person, by phone or email, with a question.  We collect your name, email address and other contact information if you register for an event.  We also collect your name, email address, telephone number and payment information when you make a contribution, either on our website, at a special event, over the phone or by mailing in a check.  The above list provides a sample of personal information that may be collected by Feeding America.  From time to time, we may collect personal information from you in ways not described above. 

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**

* We only rent or exchange lists we maintain that may include your Personal Information, collected on the website or through any other activities, with other third parties we believe engage in activities that are not inconsistent with the mission and core beliefs of Feeding America.  [You may opt out](https://www.feedingamerica.org/privacy-policy "Privacy Policy") of having your Personal Information shared by us and following the process described in our [general privacy policy](https://www.feedingamerica.org/privacy-policy "Privacy Policy").
* We will not send you mailings on behalf of other organizations.
* We will collect payment information, billing address and other information necessary to process a donation or event registration. 
* We will use your information to comply with the law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on us.  
* We will use the personal information to protect against potential fraud.  We may verify with third parties the information collected in the course of processing a gift, event registration or other donation.  If you use a credit or debit card on the website, we may use card authorization and fraud screening services to verify that your card information and address matches the information that you supplied to us and that the card being used has not been reported lost or stolen.
* You have the right to review information that we have collected about you.  To review that information please [contact us in writing](https://give.feedingamerica.org/a/contact-us).

Except as described in this Privacy Policy or at the time we request the information, we do not otherwise disclose your personal information to any third parties. 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time.  When we do, we will note the last update at the top of this Privacy Policy. 

You can learn more by reading [our general Privacy Policy](https://www.feedingamerica.org/privacy-policy "Privacy Policy").

On

Sidebar
-------

* ### [About Us](https://www.feedingamerica.org/about-us "About Us")
    
* ### [Research](https://www.feedingamerica.org/research "Research")
    
* ### [Ways to Give](https://www.feedingamerica.org/ways-to-give "Ways to Give")
    
* ### [Hunger Facts](https://www.feedingamerica.org/hunger-in-america "Hunger Facts")

* [Visit our X, formerly known as Twitter feedVisit our Twitter feed](https://twitter.com/feedingamerica "Twitter")

161 North Clark Street,  
Suite 700  
Chicago, IL 60601  

* * *

Copyright © 2024 Feeding America. All Rights Reserved. Feeding America is a 501 (c)(3) non-profit recognized by the IRS.  
Tax ID Number: 36-3673599

Photos associated with client stories feature the actual person referenced. Other images are for illustrative purposes only.
